searchsave.com 2012-11-06

# Search Save - Privacy Policy

SearchSave.com ("Search Save") is committed to safeguarding your privacy online. We will use our best efforts to ensure that the information you submit to us remains private. Please read the following policy to understand how your personal information will be treated. This policy may change from time to time so please check back periodically.

**Information Gathered About All Search Save Visitors:**  
Search Save gathers information about all of our users collectively, such as which pages users access or visit most frequently and what services users access the most. We only use such data in the aggregate. This information is used to help us improve the content of our Web Site and to continually create a better overall experience for our users. In some instances, such as when you sign up to use a service, enter into a contest, or purchase a product, we may gather more specific information about you, such as name, address, email address, telephone number, credit card number, etc. We may use this information to make you aware of additional products and services which may be of interest to you, send you our informative newsletter, offer tips on using our service or to notify you regarding updates to the Web Site. We may also ask you for other information, such as information on your interests, your likes and dislikes regarding the site, the type of jobs you are interested in, etc, in an effort to create a better overall experience for you.

**Disclosure:**  
Search Save does not share personal identifying information with any third party without permission of the user, except when we believe the law requires it, or if we sell the website as a whole (in which case all databases will be transferred with the website and the new owners will promise to follow the same policies as outlined here). Regarding information gathered about all of our users collectively, Search Save may disclose such information to third parties only in aggregate form. Also, if you input your information on a co-branded registration page, such as that of a Search Save and partner company-sponsored contest, then your information becomes the property of both Search Save and the partner co-sponsoring the contest. In that instance, Search Save is not responsible for the information that the partner company receives.

**Use Of Cookies:**  
SearchSave.com and its partners use cookies like most websites do. We use cookies to help your experience with our website. We store your searching preferences (like if you want your results in English & if you want safe search turned on). Without cookies you would have to fill out your preferences each time you search. We may also use cookies to identify you as a registered user and save you the trouble of having to log in repeatedly. We may also use cookies to serve targeted advertisements to you or otherwise assist with the functionality of our site. If you do not want to use cookies you have the option of setting your browser to refuse cookies, or you can manually delete cookies; although our website may not function normally for you if you choose to do that.

**User Submissions:**  
Users can submit information to our online "blog", forums and other areas of our site that is designed to interact with users. Personally identifiable information posted to these areas is not confidential and may be viewed by anyone with access to the Site. We are not responsible for the retention, use, or privacy of such posted information in these instances. Use by Minors: We do not specifically collect information about children. We believe that children should get their parents' consent before giving out personal information. If you are concerned about your child's use of Search Save, we encourage you to use Web filtering technology to supervise your child's access to the site. Although the vast majority of content on Search Save is intended for adults, we encourage you to participate in your child's experience with Search Save. With a little guidance, the site can prove very useful and educational.

**Unsubscribing to our email newsletters:**  
If you wish you be removed from our newsletter, simply look at the bottom of any email we sent you and click the unsubscribe link. This is the fastest and most accurate way to remove yourself from our email newsletter

If you want SearchSave.com to remove your postings or to cease any other use of personally identifiable information: you should send us a specific request by certified mail or by regular mail clearly marked "Privacy-Urgent", in either case, addressed as follows: Bill McIntosh, 19881 Brookhurst St Suite c-285 Huntington Beach, CA 92646

**Questions Or Concerns**  
Please review our complete site [terms of use](http://www.searchsave.com/terms-of-use) and [about us](http://www.searchsave.com/about-us) pages if you are concerned about your personal information. You can also [contact us](http://www.searchsave.com/contact-us) from the contact us section of our website.
